Finding aid for the Experiments in Art and Technology records, 1966-1993 (bulk 1966-1973)
Experiments in Art and Technology records
- Posters, 1966-1996; Series IX.; 39 items 1 roll and 4 flat file folders
  - 3 Posters, 1971-1996 (Oversize 12**)
    - Artists for New York Benefit, 1979
      by James Rosenquist, printed at Tandem Press, for benefit evening at Xenon, February 28, 1979; and invitation.
    - Kisses Sweeter Than Wine by Öyvind Fahlström, 1996
      For the first film in a series of documentaries from 9 Evenings: Theatre & Engineering.